let's do another quiz related to under
Sloane we still have our instruction
types of integer branch load and store
let's say now that the percentage of
execution time we spent on each is 40
percent for integer 20 percent on
branches 30 percent unloads 10% on
stores and the CPI we get for them is 1
for integer for 4 branches to 4 loads
and three for stores we have a processor
that is clocked at 2 gigahertz let's say
that we are considering the possible
improvements that are reducing the
branch CPI from 4 to 3 increase the
clock frequency of the processor from 2
gigahertz to 2.3 gigahertz and reducing
the store CPI from 3 to 2 assuming we
can only do one of these which would you
choose according to the overall speed-up